I know this is a troll comment and I shouldn't even reply to it, but let's do a history lesson,
because black people do contribute to science, they just aren't talked about or don't get the
credit for it. Example A, Mary Kenner. She created the sanitary belt before sanitary pads, but when
she tried to sell her product, she faced racial discrimination. Percy Julian created synthetic
steroids that are still used today to treat arthritis, and he created the foam that's in
fire extinguishers. Dr. Patricia Bath created the device for laser cataract surgery. Well,
Emmett Chappell created a way to see living cells under the microscope for the first time ever.
Or how about Valerie Thomas? Thanks to her, we have 3D television, and she did it with style,
and she's still alive today, but I'm guessing you haven't heard of her. If you want to take a seat,
I can keep educating you all day, but you better recognize.